Dinko Imsirovic

dimsirov@umich.edu • Ann Arbor. MI

Undergraduate Data Science student at the University of Michigan with 2+ years of experience. Passionate about turning data into insight and working not just as an analyst, but as a technologist, organizer, and communicator dedicated to bringing together technology, business, and strategy.

EDUCATION

University of Michigan

Ann Arbor, MI

Bachelor of Science in Data Science

December 2020

Coursework: Data Mining and Statistical Learning, Applied Regression Analysis, Web Systems, Computational Methods in Data Science, Data Structures and Algorithms, Introduction to Biostatistics

Programming Languages/Skills: R, Python, C++11, Microsoft Office Suite

WORK EXPERIENCE

University of Michigan *Computer Consultant II*

Ann Arbor, MI

April 2018 – August 2018

- Developed and maintained data conversion program in Google App Scripts to standardize retail product naming conventions for overhaul of primary operations database of Michigan Dining
- Successfully debugged and updated source code generating incorrect invoices in Macros and Microsoft Visual Basic under extreme time pressure to save university \$50,000

Wayne State University

Detroit, MI

Research Assistant

May 2017 – August 2017

- Spearheaded transition of research team to R/RStudio as primary statistical software with focused teaching materials and methods in the tidyverse
- Delivered improved statistical results to research team, leading to co-authorship on a publication in peer-reviewed journal (*Mito-nuclear interactions modify Drosophila exercise performance Sujkowski et. Al*)

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

University of Michigan

All-NBA Selections

Ann Arbor, MI

November 2019

- Implemented poisson regression model to predict number of times a given NBA player will be selected for the All-NBA team over the course of their career
- Collected and tidied data from different online sources to create single, appropriate dataset
- Wrangled data and developed model using dplyr and RStudio

JP Morgan Showcase Winner

March 2017 – April 2017

- Implemented machine learning and natural language processing model in Python to automate generation and tweeting of Buzzfeed quiz titles
- Engineered showmanship feature to tweet single generated title alongside randomized real titles in a multiplechoice format for patrons to guess generated title before tweeting answer

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

University of Michigan Marching and Basketball Band

Ann Arbor, MI

Trumpet

August 2016 - Present

- Reinforce marching drill and fundamentals to ensure member performance adheres to high standards of the band
- Work with staff and student leaders to create an equitable and inclusive environment within the organization

Warren Mott Boys Tennis Team

Warren. MI

Assistant Coach

August 2018 - Present

- Developed and led summer training programs to prepare varsity high school singles players for upcoming seasons
- Actively engaged with associate coaching staff and community members to optimize drills and practice sessions uniquely tailored to individuals' strengths and weaknesses